# Janhvi Jayesh Sampat

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Sex - Female (she/her) Date of Birth - 10th Dec, 1991 Nationality - Indian **Spoken Languages:** 

English (native proficiency - C2 level) Hindi (business proficiency - C1 level) Danish (limited working proficiency - B1 level)

# CONTACT DETAILS

- (a) (+45) 81 94 33 66
- (a) janhvi1012@gmail.com
- ® www.janhvi-sampat.com
- (a) Fuglegårdsvænget 92, st th 2820 Gentofte, Denmark

### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Arts (English and Sociology)

Institute of Distance and Open Learning, Mumbai University

Overall Aggregate - 79.75% Mumbai, India Sep 2018 - Jun 2021

### **Diploma in Apparel Manufacture and** Design

SNDT Women's University

Overall Aggregate - 68.60% Mumbai, India Jul 2012 - Feb 2015

### Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

Sophia College for Women

Overall Aggregate - 60.00% Mumbai, India Aug 2007 - Feb 2009

# **SKILLS**



- https://www.janhvi-sampat.com/collections.html
- https://www.janhvi-sampat.com/past-events.html

# **PROFILE**

I hold a Bachelor's degree in Arts and have work experience in the Indian fashion industry, including four years of managerial work for various brands and two years of running my own brand. Having moved to Copenhagen in 2021, I am looking to pursue a career in service design, specifically focusing on streamlining user experience with modern platforms and services.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Wolt Services Danmark ApS

https://wolt.com/en/dnk

Grocery Associate

Copenhagen, Denmark

O Processed orders from the merchant app, packed groceries, and relayed packages to courier partners.

Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Sep 2020 - Oct 2021

May 2019 - Aug 2020

Jan 2017 - Apr 2019

May 2016 - Dec 2016

May 2015 - Apr 2016 Nov 2014 - Apr 2015

O Managed internal systems and facilitated daily operations including inventory organisation and store cleaning.

**Kizo Tech LLP** 

https://www.kizo.in

Partnership and Alliance Manager

Mumbai, India

- Was in charge of partner brand onboarding and interactions for digital gift card app Kizo.
- O Performed quality control of the app (Android and iOS) through bug reporting, performance testing,
- O Identified and sourced partnership opportunities through multiple outreach strategies.
- Aligned promotional content and marketing goals through collaboration with the senior management, marketing department, and partner brands.

### Standard Apparel LLP (Rewear)

https://shop.rewear.in Chief Operating Officer

- O Designed and implemented business and marketing strategies, plans, and procedures for luxury pre-owned clothing brand, Rewear.
- Oversaw daily operations of the company including quality control, packaging and shipping, and customer care
- O Analysed and interpreted company performance metrics related to sales and customer feedback.
- Planned and participated in brand expansion activities.
- O Managed relations with partner stores, logistics partners, and garment consignors.
- O Handled copywriting duties (web and social media).

# Padma - The Label

https://www.janhvi-sampat.com/fashion.html

Founder

Mumbai, India

- o Implemented an end-to-end structure for the design, manufacture, and distribution of original prêt womenswear.
- Designed and produced multiple collections and packaging materials.
- O Conceptualised and executed campaign shoots for each collection.
- Oversaw all daily operations including budgeting, quality control, packaging and shipping, vendor sourcing and relations, and customer care.
- o Established and maintained relations with various multi-brand stores to increase distribution channels
- O Planned and participated in various on-ground marketing activities to promote brand growth and

### Think Pattern Pvt. Ltd.

https://www.payalkhandwala.in

Production Manager

Assistant Production Manager

Mumbai, India

- Planned a production schedule for womenswear fashion label Paval Khandwala.
- O Worked closely with creative director, Payal Khandwala, to help develop and produce new garment
- Analysed data received from the sales and merchandising departments to ensure that the products matched customer references, fell within established price points, and met industry norms.
- Estimated retail prices from garment samples and established quality standards.
- O Oversaw quality control of raw materials (textiles, fasteners, zippers, etc.) and finished products.
- Planned and facilitated all on-ground activities for the brand, such as campaign shoots, fashion shows, and exhibitions,
- Handled web copywriting duties.
- 4. https://www.payalkhandwala.in/ss15.php https://www.payalkhandwala.in/aw16.php https://int.payalkhandwala.shop